<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<bios>
  <bio id="Tony">
    <desc>Tony is a member of the wet lab research team. He is a 2nd year
      undergraduate at McMaster University in the Bachelor of Health Sciences
      (Honours) program. His research interests include biochemistry as well as
      multimedia-based approaches to education. Outside the lab, he is often
      found working on various graphics and video projects. His spirit creature
      is the humble potato.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Vivian">
    <desc> Vivian is head of wet lab research for iGEM McMaster 2016 and has
      recently graduated from Honours Chemical Biology co-op in April 2016. She
       is currently studying cancer immunotherapy in the Bramson lab at the
       McMaster Immunology Research Center, continuing on as a Master's
       candidate in Sept 2016. Her past experiences in industry and academia
       sparked her enthusiasm for immunology and the pursuit of a career in
       research and development. Vivian enjoys spending time with her labmates,
       sandbox video games, and board games that pit friends against one another.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Fawad">
    <desc>Mohammed (Fawad) Ahmed is the Assistant Head of iGEM McMaster, a member
      of the Wet Lab research team, and the Human Practices team. He is currently
       completing an undergraduate degree in the Biomedical Discovery and
       Commercialization (BDC) program at McMaster University. Outside of his
       program and the lab, Mohammed is a founder of the technological start-up
       company ‘Eatable’ and spends his time planning the next cool Google event
        as a Google Ambassador. In his remaining spare time, he loves watching
        mystery TV programs and cooking some very delicious food.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Clara">
    <desc>Clara is currently a third year student at McMaster, studying Health
      Sciences. She is really excited to be part of the McMaster iGEM team this
      year, as part of Human Practices, Community Outreach and as a general Wet
      Lab research member. She has some experience in different research labs,
      and she hopes to further her knowledge and learn new molecular biology
      techniques while working on this project. Her interests outside of
      synthetic biology include cheesecake and coffee.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Haley">
    <desc>Haley is involved with the McMaster iGEM’s wet lab research team and
      the community outreach and human practices subcommittees. She is currently
      completing an undergraduate degree in the Bachelor of Science (Honours) at
      McMaster University. Her areas of interest includes a wide variety of
      topics, from genetics and molecular biology to viruses.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Farhaan">
    <desc>Farhaan is a member of the public relations and business and
      development teams of iGEM McMaster. He is currently enrolled in the
      Molecular Biology and Genetics BSc program at McMaster University. This
      summer he will be completing a co-op thesis at the National Research
      Council of Canada in Saskatoon, SK. Nonetheless, he will be lending
      a helping hand when applying for team funding and regularly updating
      mGEM's Instagram page (/igemmcmaster) with pictures that give a glimpse
      into synthetic biology research and the lives of our happy team of minions.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Lauren">
    <desc>Lauren is a member of the McMaster iGEM dry lab research team.
      She has just completed her first year in the Faculty of Engineering
      at McMaster U, and hopes to continue her Bachelor of Engineering in
      the Electrical and Biomedical Engineering program. She has a strong
      interest in cardiology, electrophysiology and in immunotherapy, and
      outside of iGEM, is involved in various cardiac research projects. Her
      interests include heart failure and atrial fibrillation, as well as the
      integration of technological devices in the health care field and in
      patient self-care. In her spare time, she is an oboist for the McMaster
      Engineering Musical, plays on an intramural soccer team with her
      housemates, and enjoys spending quality time with her bunny.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Max">
    <desc>
    Max is the new team manager for McMaster iGEM, and continuing to do
      wet lab research from last year. Currently completing the Bachelor of
      Health Sciences (Honours) program, he is also fascinated by biotechnology,
       music cognition, the Titan Arums, and quantum mechanics. Other interests
       include making educational videos, playing trumpet and piano, and
       watching the thin disc of our galaxy reveal itself under a starlight night.
     </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Samaher">
    <desc>Samaher Ramzan is a wet lab research team member and part of community
       outreach . She is currently completing an undergraduate degree in
       Biotechnology at McMaster University. In addition to iGEM, her past and
       current research projects include the development of microfluidic devices
        for high content drug screening and developing sensors for monitoring
         water quality. Outside the lab Samaher is a mentor for lower year
         students, a soccer enthusiast and enjoys learning new things.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Kaijie">
    <desc>Kaijie is a member of the Dry Lab and Web Development teams for
      McMaster iGEM. He is currently studying Electrical and Biomedical
      Engineering at McMaster University, and will graduate in 2017. Kaijie
      has previously worked for Lumentra Inc., Turak Research Group, and Holland
       Bloorview Kids Rehabiliation Hospital; acquiring a variety of skills and
       assets. Beyond iGEM, he has also joined the MAC Formula Electric Team,
       and the BioEngineering at McMaster Society. In his free time, Kaijie
       develops apps, plays the piano, and competes in volleyball tournaments.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id=Beenish>
    <desc>Beenish Ajmal is a part of wet lab team in iGEM. She is currently
      finishing her undergraduate degree in bachelor's of Technology,
      Biotechnology stream at Mcmaster University. She is so into exploring
      and trying new opportunities in her life.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id=Dhany>
    <desc>Dhanyasri is part of the wet lab research team this summer and also
      manages the iGEM Facebook page. She worked with iGEM last summer on their
       previous project and learned many techniques. Her program of study is
       Integrated Science (iSci) with a specialization in chemical biology. In
       addition to iGEM, she is working on using radioisotope analysis in order
       to reveal more about the composition of bone mineral. Outside of lab
       work, Dhanyasri enjoys anime, cosplaying, and spam watching TV shows.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Chirayu">
    <desc>Chirayu (Rayu) Bhatt is a member of iGEM's wet-lab team. He is
      currently in his third year of honours biochemistry and is excited to
      begin his first year on the iGEM team. Aside from school work and lab
      work, Rayu enjoys acting and has performed with the McMaster Thespian
      Company and several other theatre productions at McMaster.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Mobeen">
    <desc>Mobeen Mubasher is a member of the community outreach and wet lab
       research team for iGEM McMaster. He is currently completing an
       undergraduate degree in the Bachelor of Health Sciences (Honours) program
        at McMaster University. Outside of the lab Mobeen enjoys living an
        active lifestyle, watching all types of anime and k-drama as well as
        eating good food!
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Jinny">
    <desc>Jinny is the head of Human Practices team of iGEM McMaster. As a
      member of the Hannah Unit in Medical Humanities at McMaster University,
      she is particularly interested in the sociological and legal factors in
      the 20th and 21st century health care in relation to concurrent
      urbanization and globalization. As a student researcher under the Forensic
       Psychiatry Program at St. Joseph's Healthcare Hamilton, Jinny plans to
       examine the impact of repetitive trans-cranial magnetic stimulation in
       the joint-field of criminal justice and psychiatry. During her spare
       times, Jinny enjoys Netflix. She is exceptionally sad that the 5th
       season of Suits hasn't aired yet.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Karanbir">
    <desc>I'm a second year Health Sciences student with a keen interest in
      bioengineering.  After school, I'm hoping to pursue a career in academic
      medicine, or maybe software engineering, or maybe something else I haven't
       discovered yet. Outside of school, hockey consumes my life.
     </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Melodie">
    <desc>Melodie is a member of the  McMaster iGEM wet lab research team.
      She has recently completed her freshman year in the Bachelor of Health
      Sciences (Honours) program at McMaster University. She has previously
      worked on identifying the roles of the ribosomal protein Der in E. coli
      and determining the mechanism of the notch signalling pathway in breast
      cancer with a particular focus on IL-23A and Th17. Currently, she is
      engrossed in iGEM as well as a research project aimed at exploring the
      relationship between the microbiome and human upper respiratory tract.
      When not in a lab, Melodie preoccupies herself with reading her favourite
      novel, watching movies, or rock climbing.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Candy">
    <desc>Candy is a member of the public relations team for iGEM McMaster. She
      is currently enrolled  an undergraduate degree in the Bachelor of Health
      Sciences (Honours) program at McMaster University. In addition to iGEM,
      she is currently working in a lab researching ALS. Outside the lab Candy
      enjoys watching tv shows and drawing.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Nicolas">
    <desc>Nicolas is a member of both the Dry Lab and Public Relations groups on
       the McMaster iGEM team. He is working towards a B.Eng in Computer
       Engineering at McMaster University. In addition to iGEM Nicolas is the
       Director of Membership for SEDS Canada and heavily interested in space
       development and robotics. He is also a video game and programming
       enthusiast.
     </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Ian">
    <desc>Ian Fare is a member of the dry lab and web development teams. He is
      enrolled in the Integrated Science program at McMaster University,
      concentrating in physics. He is also an undergraduate research assistant
      studying variable stars in globular clusters, and investigating the use
      of planetariums in university astronomy education. In his free time, he
      enjoys sewing strange costumes, programming strange games, and writing
      pretty average stories.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Ramneet">
    <desc>Ramneet Mann is the head of Community Outreach for iGEM McMaster, and
      is also an active member of the wet lab research team. She is currently
      completing an undergraduate degree in the Bachelor of Sciences at McMaster
      University. Her other research outside of iGEM McMaster includes pediatric
      emergency medicine, and arrhythmia and pacemaker studies in an electrophysiology
      lab. Ramneet is additionally a very active member of various clubs and
      services at McMaster, with a passion for diversity, multi-culturalism, and
       charity work. In her spare time, she enjoys reading fantasy and fiction
       novels such as Harry Potter and the Game of Thrones, and additionally
       enjoys playing soccer at a competitive level.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Rui">
    <desc>Rui is involved in wet lab, human practice and community outreach
      sub-teams. He is studying in the program of Honours Biology and
      Pharmacology (Co-op), McMaster University. Rui is currently working in Dr.
      Luke Janssen's lab to investigate the roles of calcium signalling in
      pulmonary fibroblasts and their relations to fibrosis. His current
      projects also include studying the localization of synaptotagmin 1/2 and
      vesicular glutamate transporter 3 in rat cerebellum. Apart from researches,
      Rui is also a member of McMaster Biology and Pharmacology Society.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Christine">
    <desc>Christine is member of dry lab for iGEM McMaster and a public
      relations team member. She is currently completing an undergraduate degree
       in the Bachelor of Health Sciences (Honours) program at McMaster
       University. Outside the lab Christine enjoys writing and is an occasional
        figure skater when the weather is cold.
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Yosef">
    <desc>Yosef is in his third year of the Bachelor of Health Sciences
      (Honours) program at McMaster University and is a Head of the Wet Lab
      team, but dabbles with the business side of iGEM as well. When he is not
      in the lab you can find him...well we’ll let you know when we find him
      outside the lab. Outside of iGEM his interests include not writing about
      himself and (insert clever sentence/random fact about self).
    </desc>
  </bio>
  <bio id="Fei">
    <desc>Fei Fei is the head of public relations for iGEM McMaster and a wet
      lab research team member. She is currently completing an undergraduate
      degree in the Bachelor of Health Sciences (Honours) program at McMaster
      University. In addition to iGEM, her past and current research projects
      include an evaluation of Pioglitazone as an antihyperglycemic agent, and
      the relationship between early life microbial and nutrient interactions
      and postnatal metabolic dysfunction. Outside the lab Fei Fei is a flautist
       for the Health Science Musical Orchestra, an avid watcher of Korean
       dramas, and enjoys recreational ice skating.
    </desc>
  </bio>
